# Jonnelin Marzielli N. Leonardo COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT

I have a passion for problem solving and recently developed a passion for computer science. I am mostly experienced in Web Development; though, I am interested in learning more about IT Security and Software Engineering.

#### **EDUCATION**

# RUTGERS UNIVERSITY, New Brunswick, NJ

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, 2014 - current

Current courses: Data Structures, Introduction to Discrete Structures

Completed courses: Introduction to Computer Science

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# STUDENT WEBMASTER, Web & Multimedia Services

Rutgers University Communications and Marketing, New Brunswick, NJ January 2016 - current

- Maintain and update websites with the Drupal Management Platform along with HTML and CSS
- Create and design website tools from scratch in collaboration with a team

## STUDENT ASSISTANT, Business Administration

Rutgers University Communications and Marketing, New Brunswick, NJ October 2015 - current

- Assist supervisors by completing any simple task given, such as filing and organizing documents.

#### **PROJECTS**

### **PRIORITIZE**

Student priority management Chrome Extension HTML, JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, Bootstrap, Google Chrome, Google Calendar, and Google OAuth APIs In Development

- A customizable calendar application that uses due dates and user priorities to create and suggest a visual schedule based on user input
- Tracks the time the user takes to finish repeated homework to calculate the average and suggest a more accurate schedule
- Uses the Google Calendar and Google OAuth APIs to synchronize and edit events in Google Calendar

#### **FLASH**

A chat room Web Application Python, Flask, SQLAlchemy, HTML, JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, Bootstrap October 2016

- A chat room application in which users can freely choose or create chat rooms to message others
- All information, including user information and messages, are saved into a database implemented in SQLAlchemy

#### **SKILLS**

Languages: HTML, CSS, Java, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Python

Web Management Software: Front-End Drupal

Version Control: Git

Operating Systems: Debian, Windows